(忆往昔)
巫术袋
Hex bag.
真恶心
Gross.
-所以是女巫  -对
- So we're thinking witch?  - Yeah.
我讨厌女巫
I hate witches.
他们总是把自己的体液吐的到处都是
They're always spewing their bodily fluids everywhere.
而且为什么老不放过兔子
And why is a rabbit alway get screwed in the deal?
可怜的小家伙
The poor little guy.
女巫
Witches.
他们是杀人凶手
They are murders.
烧死女巫
Burn witch, burn.
天哪
Oh my God!
这子弹是能杀女巫的
These are witch killing bullets.
[咒语]
罗威娜
Rowena.
我就说你会需要我
Told you you'd need me.
-我们不是一个团队吗  -不是
- Are we not a team?  - No.
(如今)
你得...不
You have to... No.
听我说
Listen to me.
快走
Get out of there.
快跑
Just go.
马上
Now.
你们这些人
You people,
就是从不吸取教训
you never learn, do you?
总是要跑
Always try to run.
[咒语]
[邪恶力量 第12季第11集]
你好啊
Hey, buddy.
(阿肯色州  尤里卡斯普林斯)
拜托
Oh, come on.
打扰  能不能...
Excuse me, do you mind if...
别拿去买酒
Just don't buy a drink.
我知道  斯黛茜
I know, Stacy.
打扰  听我说
Excuse me, look,
我不是流浪汉  好吗
I'm not a bum, okay?
我真的很需要用一下电话  可以吗
I'm just somebody who really needs to use the phone, you mind?
太好了
Great.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了
Okay.
(未知来电者)
喂
Hello?
萨姆
Sam.
哥们  你去哪了
Dude, where the hell have you been?
我也不太确定
I'm not really sure about that.
你现在在哪
You... well, where are you now?
也不确定
Not really sure about that either.
我...
I...
(沃尔多华夫饼)
我饿死了
I'm starving.
你想吃华夫饼吗
How do you feel about Waffles?
什么
What?
蠢问题  是啊
Dumb question, right.
是什么样的疯子才会不爱吃华夫饼
What psycho doesn't love waffles?
软糯糯的  浇上糖浆
I mean, they're fluffy, little pockets full of syrup
喷上奶油  是吧
and just cover with whipped cream, am I right?
总之  去沃尔多华夫饼店跟我碰面
Anyway, meet me at Waldo's, okay?
去...
Meet...
你带没带...
Did you bring any...
太好了
Yes.
看来你很需要
Sound like you could use it.
天呐
Oh man.
昨晚挺累吗
Rough night?
早上也不好过
Rougn morning.
究竟发生了什么
What happened?
你不过是出去买饭吃了
I mean, you just run out to get some food.
我不知道
I don't know.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
我一定是断片了
I guess I blacked out.
从宿醉的程度来看
And judging from this hangover.
我肯定可嗨了
It was ephic.
我给你打电话来着
Well, I tried to call you.
那个嘛...
Well...
不知道是怎么发生的
Not sure how that happened.
好吧
Right.
那好  我给妈妈发短信
All right, I'll text mom,
让她知道有情况来找我
make sure she knows to go over to me in case of an emergency.
还有小卡
And Cass,
万一他找到了凯莉
in case he tracks down Kelly.
路西法私生子的准妈妈
The mother of Lucifer's love child.
对了
Right, right.
是啊  魔鬼宝宝妈那档子事
Yes, the devil baby mama drama.
快速地说五遍试试
Say that five times fast.
魔鬼宝宝妈那档子事
Devil baby mama drama.
好吧
All right.
迪恩  那个
Dean, you know...
你也玩够了  但是
You had a good run, but...
是不是稍稍刹住点
maybe let's pump the breaks a little bit,
你已经不是二十岁了
I mean, you're not twenty anymore.
首先
Okay, one,
派对到死
you rack that party till the day they die.
其次
And B,
我还是能干翻你的
I can still kick your ass.
来点华夫饼啊
Got a man need some waffles down here.
-不  不用了  -天呐
- Oh no, I'm fine. - Oh my God.
-你来点吧  -行了  迪恩
- You just take it easy. - No, Dean,
停尸房十分钟后就开门了
look, the morgue opens in like ten minutes.
停尸房
The morgue?
尸检结果啊
You... autopsy results.
你还醉着呢吗
Are you still drunk?
应该没有
I don't think so.
好吧  我们的案子
All right, our case.
那个喉咙里被塞满了钱的
The dead guy, throat stuffed full of money.
对了...
Right, yes, right.
那个会计  巴瑞·吉尔曼
The accountant, Barry Gilman.
-对  -对了
- Right. - Right.
你觉得是恶魔干的
You think he got his ticket punched by a demon.
可能吧
Maybe.
好  但我们昨天去了他家
Okay, but we went over to his place yesterday.
什么都没发现
We got a whole bunch of jack, and a little bit of squat.
没有巫术袋  没有电磁场  没有硫磺
There was no hex bag, no EMF, no sulfur.
所以不算是案子
Which means, no case.
如果不是案子  那是怎么回事
Yeah, but if it's not a case, then what is it?
我不知道  金钱夺命吗
I don't know, death by money?
或许他是被...
Maybe the guy got whacked by a...
有黑色幽默感的黑帮分子杀了
some mob dude, with a ironic sense of humor.
好吧
All right.
我要去看看他的尸体
I'm gonna go look at the body,
如果你想再跟华夫饼单独待会儿...
if you want to spend some more alone time with waffles...
那好好玩吧
have fun.
好吧  等等
Fine, hold up.
-你付钱了吗  -好吧  嗯
- Did you pay? - Oh, well. All right.
有钱吗
Cash.
好了
Yeah, I got it.
你好吗
How are you?
嗯
Yep.
昨晚肯定老嗨了
Epic night.
谢谢
Thank you.
太好了  再有需要会叫你的
Great. We'll let you know if we need anything else.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧
All right.
正式死因是窒息
So cause of death was suffocation. Officially.
好吧  我们已经知道了
Okay. We already knew that.
"见B1-4号证据"  好吧
"See evidence bag B 1-4." All right.
说是都是从他胃里取出的
Says they pulled all this from his stomach.
早餐吃多了
Big breakfast.
好吧
Okay.
好
All right.
哎呀
Well, well.
你刚说什么黑色幽默的黑帮分子来着
You were saying about an ironic mobster?
那好吧
All right, so...
是巫师逼巴瑞吃下了一个巫术袋
a witch force feds old Barry here a hex bag
然后施了咒
and then casts a spell.
嗯  一个给他灌满了现金的咒语
Yeah, a spell that pumps him so full of cash,
他因此噎死了
he dies choking on it.
巫师啊
Witches.
人家说得对
Well, I guess it's true what they say.
没钱一身轻
Mo' money, mo' problems.
是吧
Right?
希望那还是醉话
I hope you're still drunk.
为什么会有人想要巴瑞死呢
So why would somebody want Barry dead?
他搞砸了报税表还是怎么的
I mean, what, did he screw up a tax return?
他其实是个资金经理
He's actually more of a money manager.
不管他是干啥的
Well, whatever he was,
看来他结了个厉害的...
looks like he, uh, certainly made one hell of a...
仇家吗
Enemy?
仇家  没错  就那个
Enemy. Yeah. Those guys.
或许他坑了不该坑的人的钱
Maybe he blew the wrong person's savings.
我们去查查他的客户吧
All right, well, let's check out his clients.
哪个  巴瑞为镇上最富有的一些家族工作
Which one? Barry worked for the richest families in town.
哥们  你还真是嗨翻天了  是方的那个
Man, you were serious about epic. It's the square one.
我知道...
Yeah. I know. Y--
-该死  -拜托
- Son of a bitch. - Come on!
-搞什么  -不是吧
- What the... - Really?!
对不起  怪我们
Sorry! Our fault.
我...
I...
R是倒车  迪恩
R for "reverse," Dean.
哥们  我知道我们最近挺累
Listen, man, I-I know we haven't had it easy lately.
又是魔鬼的孩子
This thing with the Devil's kid
又是被丢进了西部关塔那摩监狱
and getting tossed into West Guantanamo
有时候我也想一醉解千愁  但是...
makes me wanna crawl into a bottle, too, sometimes, but...
哥们  你真是一滩烂泥
Dude, you're wrecked.
我们还得查案呢  振作点  好吗
And we got a case to work, so get it together, all right?
迪恩
Dean?
Dean.
迪恩是谁
Who's Dean?
我说了  我没事
I told you, I'm fine.
迪恩  你连自己的名字都忘了
Dean, you forgot your own name.
就那么一下下  的确挺怪
For a second. Okay, yeah, that was weird.
听着  我们知道对手是个巫师
All right, look, we know we're dealing with a witch, right?
或许你中了巫术
Maybe you got hexed.
哥们
Dude...
如果巫师真逮到机会对付我  我早死了
if a witch got a clear shot of me, I would be dead, okay?
我不会变成...多莉
I wouldn't be freakin', uh...Dory.
-多莉  -我不会为喜欢那只鱼道歉
- Dory? - I'm not gonna apologize for loving that fish.
不管是对你还是任何人
Not to you, not to anyone.
好吧  嗯  那好
Right. Okay. All right.
如果你真没事  说出邦乔维乐队的所有成员
If you're doing so well, name all the members of Bon Jovi.
好啊
Okay.
-1983年的吗  -好啊
- We talkin' circa 1983? - Sure.
没问题  邦·乔维
Done. We got Bon Jovi.
无所谓了  这太蠢了
Whatever. This is stupid.
萨姆  我没事  我感觉很好
Sam, I'm fine. Okay? I feel great.
看...
Look, uh...
这是一把枪
This is a gun.
这是一件大衣
This is a coat.
这是...
This is a...a...a...
光棒
light stick.
光棒...
A light st--
好吧
All right.
我们需要帮助
We're gonna get you some help.
我们可以搞定的
Look, we could figure this out, okay?
别去找妈妈或小卡
Don't go callin' Mom or Cass with this.
好吧  但你好起来之前
Fine, but until you get better...
(灯)
灯  对了
Lamp. Right.
就差一点
So close.
结束悬念吧
Shall we end the suspense?
连续六局了吧
What's that? Six in a row?
新手好运
Beginner's luck.
先生们  抱歉了
Gentlemen, if you don't mind.
我有点忙呢
I'm a wee bit occupied at the moment.
我们需要你帮忙  罗威娜
Yeah, well, we need your help, Rowena.
-是吗  -拜托
- Oh, really? - Come on, man.
-罗威娜  -没错
- Rowena? I mean... - Yes. Really.
小伏特加啊  太棒了
Tiny vodkas. Score.
我现在在你的通讯录里了吗
Am I saved to your contacts now?
告诉我  我有自己的铃音吗
Tell me. Have I got my own ringtone?
这事很严重
This is serious.
迪恩好像中了巫术
Look, I think Dean's been hexed, okay?
他老是忘事情
He -- he's been forgetting things.
-或许他是喝醉了  -他不是喝醉了
- Maybe he's just drunk. - He's not drunk.
我们需要冰
We need ice.
可能是记忆咒  但他的头发脱落了吗
Could be a memory spell. But did his hair fall out?
-还有身上的毛  -什么
- His body, too? - What?
脖子以下  是不是像芭比娃娃一样光滑了
From the neck down, is he smooth like a Ken doll?
我不知道  我不会去看的
I don't know. Uh, and I'm not checking either.
那不是记忆诅咒了
Rules out a mnemonic curse.
一切忘空咒语能在一段时间内抹去一切记忆
The oblivate spell wipes the memory clean over time,
但这魔法很精妙
but it's intricate magic. I...
-怎么打破呢  -理论上
- How do I break it? - Theoretically?
杀了施咒人
Kill the witch.
知道了
Got it.
好了  迪恩
All right. So...Dean?
迪恩
Dean!
Dean?
哥们  你干什么呢
Dude, what are you doing?
弄冰  你干什么呢
Getting ice. What are you doing?
那不是我们的房间
That's not our room.
这些破地方看上去都一样
All these dumps look the same.
这个咒语  就像《记忆碎片》里那样吗
So this spell, I'm stuck in some sort of "Memento" crap?
嗯  解决方法似乎挺简单
Right. The fix sounds fairly simple.
你只需要找到下咒的巫师  杀了他
You just find the witch who did it and kill it.
太好了
Oh, halle-freakin'-lujah.
-我觉得你昨晚中了巫术  -是吗
- I think you got hexed last night. - Yeah?
嗯  我们得回溯你的经历
Yeah, we need to retrace your steps.
好吧  想想
All right, think.
你记得你做的最后一件事是什么
What's the last thing you remember you did?
去弄冰
I got some ice.
好吧  昨天
Okay, from yesterday,
我最后大概记得的事就是
the last thing I kinda sorta remember is
我们来这儿
us being here
这是...
in, um...
那哥们办公室
big guy's office.
-巴瑞·吉尔曼  -没错
- Barry Gilman. - Yes. And...
我们来这儿找线索
we were here and we were, uh, we were looking for leads.
嗯  二货税
Yeah. Douche tax.
嗯  你昨天也那么做了
Yeah, you did that yesterday, too.
来  看这个
All right, come here. Check these out.
这些照片让你想起来什么没
Do these shake anything loose, these pictures?
没有  完全没有
No. None of them.
好好想想  接下来呢
Okay, think hard. What happened next?
我去查传说了  你出去吃汉堡了  然后...
I went to hit the lore. You went out for a burger. So...
然后...
So...
你要我说什么  我吃了汉堡吗
What do you want me to say? I-I ate 'em?
好吧  这样  这里不大
Okay, okay. You know what? It's not a big town.
能有多少家汉堡店啊  走吧
How many burger joints can there be? Come on.
(骑公牛)
好吧  记起什么了吗
All right. Anything?
没有  这都第三家了
No. I mean, this is the third place we've been to.
我...没印象...
I-I...No. It's...
等等
Wait.
是她  华夫饼店那个
It's -- it's her from, uh, from the waffles.
来吧
All right, come on.
打扰
Excuse me.
你要是想道歉  最好快点的
If you're gonna apologize, you better make it quick.
我道歉  是你打了我
Me apologize? Uh, you smacked me.
-是你犯浑  我们扯平了  -扯平什么
- You were being a dick. We're even. - Even for what?
不管你的...你是谁
That's none of your -- Who are you?
听着  不管我们是怎么了  对不起  好吗
Okay, look, whatever happened with us, um, I'm sorry. Okay?
是这样的  我们...
See, here's the deal. We're, um, we're...
我们是联调局的  穆恩和恩威瑟探员
We're FBI. Uh, Agents Moon and Entwistle.
-联调局  -是啊
- FBI? - Yeah.
你昨晚还说你叫斯普林斯汀呢
Last night, you told me your name was Springsteen.
跟"老板"一样
Like The Boss.
有时候我们得撒谎
Yeah, see, sometimes, we have to lie in order to, uh,
好掩护身份
to... protect our cover.
-不会吧  -好吧  这事很敏感
- No way. - Okay, listen, this is actually sensitive.
我们认为我搭档可能被下了药
We -- we think my partner may have been roofied.
-不是吧  -不是吧
- Seriously. - Seriously?
如果你能告诉我们那晚发生了什么
If you can tell us anything about what happened that night,
会对我们大有帮助
it would be a big help.
-好吧  我...  -太好了
- Sure. I... - Great.
他点了汉堡带走
He ordered burgers to go.
我要他等一会儿  当时人多
It was gonna be a minute. We were slammed.
然后你喝了...四杯龙舌兰吧
Then you knocked back... four shots of tequila?
还点了些挺"酷"的音乐
Put some "sick jams" on the juke,
然后上了公牛
and then you hit the bull.
-他什么  -我什么
- He what? - I what?
是啊  你一走进来
Oh, yeah, you had the hots for Larry
就看好拉瑞了
as soon as you walked in here.
他...你骑了拉瑞
He -- You rode Larry?
我厉害吗
Was I good?
你可厉害了
You were...amazing.
总之
Anyway,
我们聊了起来
we got to talking, and...
你懂的
you know.
我们活动了下筋骨
We blew off some steam.
你看到他跟别人说话了吗
Did you see him talk with anyone else?
我的酒保说他急匆匆地跑了出去
My bartender said she saw him run out of here
就像裤子着火了一样
like his pants caught fire.
但我们说好关门后碰面的
We were supposed to meet up after close-up,
可你根本没来
but you never showed.
小可怜  你被人下了药啊
Poor thing. You were all roofed up.
我不知...
I didn't...
我真抱歉
I am so sorry
不是有意占你便宜的
if I took advantage of you.
没事
It's okay.
这地方有监控吗
Does this place have security cameras?
有
Yeah.
好久以来第一次搞上妹子
First action in I don't know how long,
结果却完全不记得  真是的
and it's like it never even happened. Figures.
这就很好笑了
See, now that's comedy.
-好吧  那是我  -嗯
- Okay, whoa. There I am. - Yeah.
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
我在读我的唇语
I'm trying to read my lips.
"现在莎莎舞你连指手套"
"Now salsa you mittens""
你不会读唇语
You can't read lips.
我不会读唇语
I can't read lips.
看到了吗
You see that?
当然  这应该就是巫师
Yeah, of course. I think we got our witch.
你记得这一切吗
What, you don't remember any of this?
就好像在网飞上看自己一样
It's like watching myself on Netflix.
(吉尔曼  吉尔伯特事务所)
那人眼熟吗  那件外衣
That guy look familiar to you? That jacket?
算了  蠢问题
Never mind. Stupid question.
巴瑞办公室里好像有张他的照片
I think Barry had a picture of him in his office.
可能你昨晚就是这样认出了他
It might be how you recognized him last night.
我还开了一枪
And I take a shot.
我会开枪吗
I know how to shoot a gun?
好吧
All right, so...
你撞在了这儿
you crashed there.
你往那边跑了
You ran that way.
开枪
Shot, uh...
这里
Here.
嗯
Yep.
杀巫师的子弹
Witch-killing bullet.
等等
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
这世上还有巫师
There are witches?
迪恩
Dean...
巫师是真的
witches are real.
吸血鬼  狼人  巫师  都是真的
Vampires, werewolves, witches, they're all real.
我们要杀他们
And we kill them.
太棒了  这太棒了
Awesome. That's awesome.
好吧  好吧
Right. Right.
走吧
Come on.
好吧  等等  灯神不满足愿望
Okay, so wait. So -- so djinns don't grant wishes,
海妖并非都是辣妹
and sirens aren't all hot chicks?
是啊  抱歉戳破你的幻想
Yeah. Sorry to break it to you.
-真是疯了  -怎么了
- This is crazy. - What?
我居然来给你做"教育"
Me giving you "The talk""
知道我们有多少次不得不告诉普通平民
You know how many times we've had to tell some civilian
-怪物是真的吗  -但怪物的确是真的
- that monsters are real? - Yeah, but monsters are real.
我们是杀他们的人
And we're the guys that kill 'em, man.
拜托  这工作太棒了
I mean, come on. Best job ever.
是啊  如果你喜欢油腻腻的餐馆食物
Yeah. If you like greasy diner food,
破烂的旅馆房间  不止一次的天启
crappy motels rooms, more than one Apocalypse.
我不知道  听上去我们是英雄
I don't know. We kinda sound like heroes to me.
我们最好的朋友还是个天使
And our best friend's an angel.
老天爷
What?!
我们得赶紧治好你
We just gotta get you cured.
嗯  好
Yeah. Okay.
这个  太诡异了
Okay, now, these? Freaky.
不  那只是雕文
No, they're just, uh, glyphs.
巫师在施咒时会用到  但我
Witches use them in spells, but I've actually
从没见过这样的
never seen anything like this before.
或许罗威娜能认出来
Maybe Rowena will recognize 'em.
或许吧  罗威娜是谁  好奇怪的名字
Maybe. Who's Rowena? That's a weird name.
萨姆
S-S-Sam!
Sam!
怎么了
What?
那是个死人吗
Is that a dead guy?
嗯  那应该就是我们找的巫师
Yeah. I think that's our witch.
太酷了
Cool.
不  迪恩  杀死巫师本该是解决办法的
No, Dean. Killing the witch was supposed to be the cure.
如果他已经死了  那你为什么...
So if he's already dead, then why aren't you...
还不是你
you?
不妙
Not cool.
好吧  那怎么办
Okay, what now?
我们离开这里  走
Now we get out of here. Let's go. Come on.
好
Okay.
猎人
Hunters.
可怜的吉迪恩
Poor Gideon.
所以他叫我们别去动那个会计师的
This is why he told us to leave the accountant alone.
那混蛋偷了我们的东西
That tub of guts stole from us.
他是罪有应得
He deserved what he got.
他们发现我们了  凯特  我们得跑了
They're on us, Cat. We have to run.
我才不要跑
I am not going to run!
我也不管吉迪恩说了什么
And I don't care what Gideon said.
怎么  你还想杀了他们吗
So what? You wanna kill them, too?
我想要回我的家人
I want my family back.
那是个死人吗
Is that a dead guy?
是啊
Yeah.
从没见过死人呢
Never seen a dead guy before.
你见过的  相信我
Yeah, you have. Trust me.
别  迪恩  等等
No, D-Dean, wait a second.
你是谁
Who are you?
看来中咒程度又加深了
Spell's progressed, I see.
你...
You --
我要的是情报  罗威娜  不是上门服务
I wanted intel, Rowena, not a house call.
我感觉你会谢谢我的
Oh, I have a feeling you'll come to thank me.
你的头发  好有弹性
Your hair, it's all so bouncy.
谢谢
Why, thank you.
我们非要治好他吗
Do we have to fix him?
-罗威娜  -萨穆埃尔
- Rowena. - Samuel.
你们发现的雕文是古凯尔特语
Those glyphs you found are an archaic form of Celtic.
欧甘文支
Ogham Chraobh.
德鲁伊人将其用于他们的仪式
The Druids used it in their rituals,
称之为"树的语言"
calling it the "Language of the Trees."
等等  树还会说话了
Wait, wait. Now the trees are talkin'?
迪恩  你记得HBO吗
Dean, do you remember HBO?
电影频道
Cinemax?
成人电影频道
Skinemax.
很好  过来
Great. All right, come here.
我们...
We're just gonna
你坐在这里
We're gonna sit you down right here.
嗯  来...
And, uh, yeah, go ahead.
这是要成人电影直播吗
This like live Skinemax or...
二怎么样
How 'bout two?
太棒了  坐着别动
Perfect. Stay there.
过来
Come here.
只有一个巫师家族
There's only one family of witches
善用这种魔法
versed in this kind of magic.
我以为他们早死绝了
I thought them all dead for years, but
但看到那雕文后
when I saw those glyphs...
这是其中之一吗
Is this one of 'em?
吉迪恩·洛克兰
Gideon Loughlin.
你认识他吗
Did you know him?
算是吧
A bit.
好吧  跟我讲讲他们家
All right, tell me about this family.
一百年前
A hundred years ago,
洛克兰家族从旧世界迁至这里
the Loughlins came over from the Old World and
将密西西比三角洲的一个小镇
turned a small town on the Mississippi Delta
变成了他们自己的地盘
into their own personal fiefdom.
他们的孩子  吉迪恩  博伊德和凯特琳娜
Their children -- Gideon, Boyd, and Catriona --
就像一棵树上结的三个烂果子
were like three rotten little peas in a pod.
这家人有一本强大的咒语书
The family possessed a powerful spell book,
德鲁伊魔法典籍  《黑魔法书》
a tome of Druidic magic called the Black Grimoire.
来自世界各地的巫师去跟他们同住
Witches came from around the world to live with them
学习其中奥秘
and study its secrets...
但要付出代价
for a price.
他们怎么了
So what happened to 'em?
猎人
Hunters happened.
当然了  我听说有一两个活了下来
Of course, I'd heard rumors one or two survived,
带走了他们的书
stealing away with their book,
但我只当作是谣言
but I-I dismissed them as gossip.
吉迪恩死了
With Gideonn dead
如果你想打破你哥哥中的咒
if you want to break the curse on your brother,
我们得找到那本书
we need to find that book.
等等  你不能打破吗
Wait a second. So you can't break it?
当然可以
Oh, of course I could,
但如此复杂的巫术需要时间
but witchcraft this complex would take time,
而迪恩剩的时间不多了
more than Dean's got.
他已经开始遗忘自己了
He's already begun to forget himself,
还有他认识  爱过的每个人
everyone he's ever known, ever loved.
甚至是你
Even you.
很快他会忘记如何说话  如何吞咽
Soon he'll forget how to speak, how to swallow,
然后
and then...
迪恩·温彻斯特会死的
Dean Winchester's going to die.
那哥们好惨
Sucks for that guy.
那么经历了那么多事
So after everything...
我要死在这事上了
That's it. This is what nails me.
不不  迪恩
No. No, no, Dean, it...
不会那样的
It's not gonna happen, all right?
你刚跟我说了我一生的故事
Well, you just told me my whole life story.
老实说  我感觉得到
And I gotta be honest, man, I...I can feel it,
我在渐渐遗忘
slipping out of my head.
杀怪物是一码事  但这...
I mean, ganking monsters is one thing. But this...
我们会...
You know, uh, we're gonna, um...
我们会有办法的  好吗
We'll figure it out. All right?
我们会的
We will.
他怎么样了
How is he?
你真关心吗
Like you care.
我见过我哥哥死  但是
You know, I've seen my brother die, but
看着他变得
watching him become...
不像他自己
not him...
这恐怕更糟
This might actually be worse.
好吧
Okay.
我叫迪恩·温彻斯特
My name is Dean Winchester.
萨姆是我弟弟
Sam is my brother.
玛丽·温彻斯特是我妈妈
Mary Winchester is my mom.
卡西...
And Cast--
小卡是我最好的朋友
Cass is my best friend.
我们得找到那本魔法书
We need to find that grimoire.
当然
Of course.
当然  这就是你的目的吧
Of course. That's your angle, isn't it?
得了  罗威娜
Oh, come on, Rowena.
出现了厉害的魔法书
A powerful spell book shows up
你突然就跑来帮忙了
and all of a sudden, you're here to help?
利他主义并非你的风格
Altruism isn't exactly your style.
是啊
True.
而且  让温家人欠你个人情总是好事
Also, it never hurts to have a Winchester owe you one.
我叫迪恩·温...
My name is Dean Wi--
温彻斯特
Winchester.
我叫...
My name -- my name is...
我...
My... .
我叫...
My name is -- is...
吉迪恩·洛克兰的地址在他会计师的档案里
Gideon Loughlin's address was in his accountant's file.
如果书在他那儿  我能找到
If the book is there, I'll find it.
当然了  你会需要我帮忙
Of course, you'll need me there to help --
不不  你留下陪迪恩
No, no, you're staying here with Dean.
我才不要
I most certainly am not.
他不能跟我来  我也不能丢下他一人
Well, he can't come with me, and I'm not leaving him alone.
我显然并不信任你
And I obviously don't trust you.
显然的
Well, obviously.
《黑魔法书》是用古德鲁伊语写的
The Black Grimoire's written in ancient Druid.
要是没有我  你怎么能找到
How do you propose to find a proper spell
合适的咒语来...
without me there to --
你说洛克兰家还有几个人活下来了
Well, you said a few of the Loughlins survived, right?
谣传是如此
That was the rumor?
你指望他们家的人来...怎么
So you expect one of them to -- to what?
为你翻译他们的远古绝密咒语书吗
Translate their ancient super secret family spell book for you?
你刚杀了他们的兄弟
You just killed their brother.
他们更想剥了你的皮当衣服穿
They'd sooner use your skin as an outfit.
让他们试试吧
They can try.
我...
My...my...
我不知道
I don't know.
别乱碰了
Stop touching everything.
抱歉
Sorry.
来
Here.
拿这个玩
Play with this,
我给你讲个故事
and I'll tell you a story.
好
Okay.
从前  有个美丽的女巫
Once, a beautiful witch was,
被一群自大  自命不凡
again, run out of her homeland
来势汹汹的混混赶出了家乡
by those pompous, self-righteous, murderous hooligans.
他们就是英国记录者
You know them as The British Men of Letters.
她去一个巫师家庭寻求庇护
She sought refuge with a family of witches.
她不过是想要个住处
All she wanted was a roof over her head
一个供她磨练魔法的安全之所
and a safe place to hone her magic.
但他们把她赶了出去
Yet, they threw her out like...
就好像她是垃圾  说她没那个本事
like common trash. Said she wasn't up to snuff.
这些巫师听上去真浑
Oh, these witches sound like dicks.
我觉得你特别有本事
I think you got plenty of snuff.
你真是什么都不记得了  是吧
You can really remember nothing, can you?
能不记得自己做过的事真是恩赐啊
What a gift not to recall the things you've done.
我做过什么
What have I done?
你是个杀手  迪恩·温彻斯特
You're a killer, Dean Winchester.
里面有谁
Who's inside?
等等  我杀人
Wait, I...I kill people?
好多呢
Scores.
但是
But...but...
你虽然是个顽固的讨厌鬼
though you may be a stubborn pain in the arse
而且毫无礼貌可言
with the manners of a Neanderthal
吃饭像个三岁孩子
and the dining habits of a toddler,
你做的一切
everything you've done, you've done...
都是为了大局
for the greater good.
那么就没事了吗
Oh, and that's supposed to make it okay?
我可不知道
I wouldn't know.
你帮助他人
You help those other than yourself.
但我呢
But me?
我做过可怕的事
I've done horrible things,
还安慰自己那没事
and I told myself it was fine.
那是权力的代价  权力才最重要  是吧
It was the price of power. And power's what matters, right?
然后我遇见了上帝和他妹妹
Then I met God and his sister.
全宇宙最厉害的两个人物
The two most powerful beings in the universe,
居然浪费权力跟彼此拌嘴
wasting it on squabbling with each other.
我想  如果他们都不开心
I thought, if -- if they can't be happy,
甚至满足
or at least satisfied,
那我还有什么希望
how can there be any hope for me?
你为什么跟我说这些
Why are you telling me this?
因为我知道你不会记得的
Because I know you won't remember.
(萨姆·温)
你进去了吗
You're in?
对  进去了
Yeah, I'm in.
好
All right.
等我拿到翻译
As soon as I get the translation,
你就施咒
you cast the spell.
这枪里都是杀巫师的子弹
This gun is full of witch-killing bullets.
你去找你的魔法书
So why don't you go to your grimoire
告诉我怎么打破记忆咒
and tell me how to break the memory spell?
我就说你会来
I told him you'd come.
博伊德想去找你  但我说  "何必"
Boyd wanted to go after you, but I said, "Why bother?"
你们是猎人
You're hunters.
你们会来找我们
You'll hunt us down,
找上门来
right at our doorstep.
像披萨一样新鲜得热气腾腾
Hot and... fresh like pizza.
我不会再说一遍了
I'm not asking you again.
[咒语]
萨姆
Sam?
你弟弟被巫师绑架了
"Your brother's been kidnapped by a witch.
我找到了你的破车  把你丢在了这儿
I found your stupid car and left you here."
破
Stupid?
好吧
Okay.
(别乱跑)
别乱跑
"Stay."
博伊德  你保证过的
Boyd, you promised.
没有吉迪恩  我们就不是一家人
Without Gideon, we are not a family.
你背着他把那个会计
Well, you should've thought of that before
变成彩罐之前就该想到这点的
you went behind his back and pinata'd the accountant.
吉迪恩叫你别纠结的
Gideon told you to let it go.
就让我们被一个一无是处的人类欺骗吗
And let us be cheated by some sniveling, weak human nothing?
你害死了我们的哥哥
You got our brother killed.
我们
Well, we...
可以复活他
can bring him back.
动手
Do it.
求你  为了我
Please. For me?
凯特琳娜·洛克兰
Catriona Loughlin.
岁月无情啊
The years have not been kind.
你是谁
Who are you?
罗威娜
Rowena.
罗威娜·麦克劳德
Rowena MacLeod?
你不想这么做的
You don't wanna do this.
哎呦呦
Well, well, well.
看是谁醒了
Look who's awake.
不管你妹妹计划了什么
Okay, so whatever your sister has planned,
你不用那么做的
you don't have to do it.
用你的灵魂换他的吗
You mean, swapping your soul for his?
恐怕我非得做
I'm afraid I do.
破烂娃娃
Raggedy Ann.
什么
Excuse me?
我记得你
I remember you --
在我们门口蜷成一团的破娃娃
a rag doll all huddled up on our doorstep.
我发誓我能看到虱子啃食着
I swore I could see the fleas nibbling away
你那具残破
at whatever the hell was left of that
肮脏的驱壳
dirty little body of yours.
可是
And still...
你还觉得自己配学习我们的魔法
still, you thought you were worthy of our magic.
我们提出异议时
And when we disagreed...
你那么哀求我们
how you begged,
毫不顾忌面子
how you threw yourself down and...
要向我们每个人献身
offered yourself to each of us.
博伊德差点就心动了
Boyd almost took you up on it, too.
但我说  上只猪都更干净
But I told him, it would be cleaner with the pigs.
知道人怎么说吗
You know what they say?
没有什么比撕开新伤口更能治愈老伤口
Nothing heals old wounds like opening fresh ones.
(别乱跑)
(打开我)
(不行)
(杀巫师的子弹)
(这把枪)
∮ 我就是个小姑娘  小破烂娃娃 ∮
∮ I'm just a little girl, I'm Raggedy Ann. ∮
∮ 破烂娃娃 ∮
∮ Oh, Raggedy Ann. ∮
∮ 快要散架 ∮
∮ Falling apart. ∮
∮ 线也开裂 ∮
∮ At the seams. ∮
我一向不太会投飞镖
I've never been very good at darts.
再来
Do over.
∮ 就是个小姑娘  破烂娃娃 ∮
∮ Just a little girl, Raggedy Ann. ∮
∮ 破烂娃娃 ∮
∮ Oh, Raggedy Ann. ∮
枪
A gun?
你真觉得那杀得了一个...
You really think that's gonna work on a...
(杀巫师的子弹)
不不  弟弟  巫师
No, no, no. Brother. Witch.
行了吗  好了吗
Is that it? Is -- is it done?
这小子是谁
Who's this hippie?
看他的表情啊
Look at his face.
就像我把你的万圣节糖果都吃掉了的那次
Kind of like the time when I ate all your Halloween candy.
记得吗  太经典了
You remember that? Classic.
不好笑
Not funny.
你居然叫来了罗威娜
I can't believe you called Rowena.
你居然骑了拉瑞
I can't believe you rode Larry.
我在那头公牛上很厉害的
I was awesome on that bull.
就像神一样
I was like a god.
如果你记起了什么中咒期间
Now, should you experience any odd memories
奇怪的记忆  或对话
from when you were hexed, conversations,
就告诉我
you let me know?
大部分都不记得了  真的
It's blank, mostly. Really.
等等
Oh, just a second.
如果你想感谢我  给我寄个礼品篮就好
If you want to thank me, you can send a wee gift basket.
书
The book.
你真没劲
You're no fun.
我们欠你个小人情
We owe you one. Small one.
咒语解除后你感觉还好吗
So how you holding up after the spell?
那玩意把我整的好惨
That thing kicked my ass.
老实说
You know, I gotta be honest.
我起初有点嫉妒
I was actually, uh, a little jealous at first.
嫉妒什么  差点害死我的咒语吗
Of what? The curse that nearly killed me?
不是  就是
No, just, you know...
我们做的一些事  一直是我们的负担
some of the things we've done, we've had this weight for...
已经很久了
Forever.
看到那消失  你是那么开心
And seeing it gone, uh, you looked happy.
丢掉负担是不是好事呢
Look, was it nice to drop our baggage?
或许吧  很可能是
Yeah, maybe. Hell, probably.
但遗失的不止是烂事
But it wasn't just the crap that got lost.
而是一切
I mean, it was everything.
我们  我们的工作  那一切
It was us, it was what we do, you know? All of it.
所以...
So...
如果那就是开心的样子
that's what being happy looks like?
我还是算了
I think I'll pass.
-是亮亮的那个  -上车吧
- It's the, uh, the shiny one that's - Get in the car.